[Music]
there's someone - not a sound system
works where's leo
[Music]
here we go
[Applause]
[Music]
right
[Applause]
[Music]
so as you know this is unprecedented I
don't think there's ever been anything
like this in the United States before
where ordinary citizens like us have
come out in solidarity with the elected
government of a country to protect it
from
neo-cons and folks in the White House
who are orchestrating this whole thing
so here we are people power and what
better place to be than in the Chavez
library that's paying the Empire and I
feel Chavez smiling at us right now and
certainly the eyes of Chavez are looking
down on us as we are here so we want to
start this out with a representative of
the Venezuelan government well in the
Deputy Foreign Minister we'd love to be
here with us but he is in New York with
the part Minister and want to send us a
message
[Music]
standing up for international law the
warping of the Venezuelan embassy in
Washington important to hear your voices
to hear Paul for the respect of national
sovereignty with respect as well as
Parker will and for safeguarding to have
friends in the United States that are
standing up for justice and are standing
up for what's right and for the respect
of the will of the people were let's
hear that you were a meaning constantly
in the embassy and you have made it a
place where the paint democracy dialog
can really be established and can really
flourish hopefully this is
maintain in our premises for a long time
I know today our meeting you have a very
important educational meeting to talk
about a way that our region Latin
America has been constantly intervene by
foreign forces and by foreign interests
that have attempted against democracy
and against social justice so hopefully
today will be a very fulfilling
encounter and that you know we help each
other to understand our region and to
make sure that our countries are
respected dimensional ball and respect
justice so thank you very much for being
there
[Music]
[Applause]
we're sandy can't be United States
Carlos was tremendously helpful to us
when we were to Venezuela recently on so
many levels I'm sure others who've been
developed on the same thing he was never
seen such a big smile on somebody's face
when we were walking he was with us
walking down the hall he just lovely so
we appreciate Carlos greatly my name's
Kevin Zeese by the way and with no
resistance services outside very openly
showing their presence their
intimidation but we know we're not
intimidated and the secret please I
guess the Secret Service in the backyard
early this morning
taking pictures of buildings Vivian
Benjamin and I went out and spoke with
them to see what was up and they were
very vague they said that they were not
planning to enter embassy I said I'm
doing the job that the US government
should be doing and we've been here for
quite a while and we plan to stay here
for the foreseeable future until
Venezuela United States to talk to each
other I know that sounds so minimal that
we are talking to a adolescent president
I'll talk to each other and work out a
relationship there's also an embassy in
Venezuela Caracas the USM is vacant so
the event is longer we do something
there we don't think so and I hope they
don't we don't want to see that content
pretend that escalates into a conflict
but we're here as civilians particularly
embassy to stand up the Vienna
Convention is stand against trespass to
stand against the coup a coup that has
failed in Venezuela I know they know
he's a u.s. puppet they'd always to hide
to the US government
we know the economic problems they're
facing are coming with the US government
you know the electrical grid the attack
is coming for the US government and only
attempted assassination of President
Maduro tinea from the US
they know that Windows chief of staff
and plans for terrorism in the United
States paid for by the US government a
billion dollars the u.s. blamed on
spending of money seized from Venezuela
to cause chaos in Venezuela with
terrorism this has all come out of
documents cell phones computer seized
from Wanga why those chief of staff and
bodyguard they were planning a bring in
mercenaries from Central America trained
in Colombia funded through the Bank of
America dressed in military uniforms of
the Venezuelan government to try to
pretend that the military is opposed to
the military supports reading some of
these pictures here and there's this
second picture the fourth picture he's
reading the Venezuelan Constitution
there so we're standing with the
Venezuelan people in solidarity and so
tonight we have a really fantastic show
for you a credible speaker well I'm not
gonna introduce I'm gonna do somebody
else who was very important to us as
well the lawyer one of the lawyers for
the embassy protection collective moral
Fair Haven Hilliard constitutional
lawyer well-known in Washington DC
directs the partnership for civil
justice fund as to the many cases that
have expanded the rights
protesters in Washington DC and she's
here on behalf of our collective wants
to give you a few words with people from
all over the United States to spin here
to stay in this building and to stand up
while it's called the embassy protection
collective it's a collective standing up
for human rights for democracy for
international law are not standing up
for so these are people of the United
States who are fighting for the things
that we awoke dear and the Vienna
Convention as Kevin mentioned is what
mutters international buildings
diplomatic structures and relations
under the Vienna Convention and embassy
is enviable even if there are bad
relations even if relations break down
the US government cannot just cease the
embassy at its whip now as Kevin
mentioned the Secret Service has been
coming here they have been threatened by
State Department representatives and we
want to send a very clear message a very
clear message which is that everyone is
here is here lawfully at the invitation
of the people lawfully in charge of this
building which is owned by the
government of Venezuela second there are
laws in the District of Columbia that
protect people from eviction and people
have been staying here and sleeping here
and have been here for a long period of
time in order for the government to move
to remove people under eviction there
were due process requirements and have
not been met there's been no notice it's
been no due process there's been no
opportunity to challenge and attempted
eviction so the message that we want to
say to every single State Department
official to every Secret Service Officer
danwon police officer in the
metropolitan Police Department and the
US Marshal to anyone who is thinking
about taking action against the people
who are lawfully present in this
building
it is our view it's the view of the
collective that any such action is an
unlawful act anyone then orders or
effectuates or carries out an unlawful
act an unlawful seizure or an unlawful
arrest of any person who is standing up
for democracy for human rights and
against their government this government
the government of the United States
illegal pas so for all the people who
are present here today and were staying
strong I want to say it's an amazing
amazing event and it's an amazing signal
and message to the US government that
the people of the United States will not
fold and will not be cowed and will not
be friend with illegal actions
[Applause]
Thank You Maura thanks to everyone here
and to all of the people who are
watching us on Facebook livestream all
of the those people who have responded
in the last days in the last week's to
the appeal from the collective a real
special I would say death of gratitude
from all of the all of us in the
progressive movement
[Applause]
but frankly without their having been
the anchor for this collective this
would not actually be able to happen so
it shows that individuals and
organizations but even small numbers of
individuals make a difference
that's how progressive movements start
people say oh you're so small popular
you've actually changed well of course
you're swell until you get bigger we
co-hosted daily two-hour show on radio
Sputnik called Bobby clear which is I'm
Washington DC radio stations other
stations and it's a podcast in many
places and you know it's been a real
it's been very very interesting of
course to work together every day to
evaluate assess analyze have great
guests on amazing experience for those
of us presenting on here but I have to
say in the last days we see Google has
taken down Press TV
we see Thomas or Undertown we see our G
and Sputnik required to register as
foreign agents we see Facebook and other
social media taking down alternative
media because without the alternative
media the American people and people
generally cannot possibly learn the
truth because the function of corporate
owned media is not to tell the truth but
the function is an echo chamber for us
[Applause]
John and I realized that we know the
same things about the same events over
the past thirty years but because he was
in the CIA and I was organizing against
the CIA in here we know things from a
completely different point of view
originally but what brings us together
is again what the US government actually
did and what they did to John Kiriakou
and when they're doing to Julian Assange
and Chelsea Manning and other
whistleblowers John Kiriakou went from
being somebody who was considered
legitimate in the Washington political
circles to Prasanna non grata and
actually a federal prisoner because he
committed a great crime he was the one
member of the CIA the one who told the
truth to the American people that the
CIA was engaged in a massive torture
program that George W Bush was lying
when he told the American people that
torture didn't exist
and because of that not the torturers
but the person who revealed the torture
was sent to prison and that's how John
Kiriakou and myself in a way of men our
paths crossed because John Kiriakou like
anyone who dares as an act of conscience
to tell the truth about US government
illegality or criminal conduct becomes
target a target in their crosshairs just
like the Venezuelan government is a
target in their crosshairs or the
Iranian government or alternative media
you name it the US government says that
they only have puppets and proxies
around the world but we want free
thinking human beings who can come
together and show not profit or
exploitation but genuine human
solidarity and cooperation can be the
watchword of our species
based on personal experience with and
great knowledge of the CIA is now going
to talk about the topic at hand which is
that the u.s. government has
relentlessly
enduringly and comprehensively been
engaged in the interference in other
countries democratic processes not
simply trying to overturn elections but
kill the leaders aren't imprison the
leaders who are elected by their own
people but who don't follow the dictates
of Washington it's a great honor to
introduce John
[Applause]
I have learned more from Brian Becker in
the last year and a half that I think
I've learned from anybody in my life
also think Wow a bunch of people the
Venezuelan government the Venezuelan
foreign ministry the Venezuelan embassy
right here where we're celebrating
freedom and democracy like the thin code
pink and everybody who's been involved
in this righteous event I also would
like to invite the Secret Service to
come in I want to start by talking to
you about a normal event in the daily
life of a CIA officer and I'm going to
use a real-life example I worked in the
CIA's Counterterrorism Center for a long
time both before and after the 9/11
attacks and I had an idea it's kind of a
dumb idea but you know what you do is
you you throw out 30 dumb ideas and
maybe one of them was good give him
motive for it so I went up to the
director of counterterrorism this was
cover black later ambassador Cofer black
big muckety-muck and I said Cofer I want
to talk to you about an idea that I had
for an operation he put up his hands he
said listen whatever you want to do just
do it I have so much money I can't
simply spend it all story so I did it
I wasted fifty thousand dollars the
taxpayers money we've got a couple
business class trips to Europe out of it
but that's normal business of the CIA
they have so much money that they can't
possibly spend it on and the way that
they get promoted is to do things like
overthrow governments that sounds awful
right just out of curiosity I went on
the internet today to see how many
governments did the CIA actually
overthrew just as a CIA operation I'm
not talking about sending troops I'm not
talking about what twenty years of
economic sanctions I'm talking about the
CIA and acting a policy or program to
overthrow a legitimate government it
starts off with seven it starts off with
seven and those seven are and I'm going
to tell you as soon as I turn a page
Iran 1953 we're still paying for that
stupid idea we overthrew that government
when we became British Petroleum just
for the money because the Brits asked us
to because they were telling me to do it
themselves and they said well the
Americans will do it for us and we did
here we are three generations later and
people are still dying because of that
stupid decision Guatemala 1954 Congo
1960 Dominican Republic 1961 South
Vietnam 1963 Brazil 1964 to late 1973
you see anything here that may be a
pattern that we overthrow these
governments and they're taken over
usually for many many decades by either
fascist dictators or military windows I
call that failure I wouldn't call that a
successful foreign policy now on
curiosity how many countries has the US
government tried to overthrow since the
end of the Second World War
there's actually a number
Medicus like plain blue how many 41 42
57 countries man I'm a greek-american
very proudly so and I have lots and lots
of cousins still in Greece who lived
through the military dictatorship there
there's a word for it in Greek it just
means the seven years because those
seven years were so terrible and so many
people died that they can't even bring
themselves to call it anything else but
the seven years and all you have to say
is the seven years and everybody knows
what you're talking about tanks in the
streets shooting rounds into college
campuses slaughtering people wholesale
somewhat to overthrow a democratically
elected government to install a military
dictatorship that suspends all human
rights civil liberties for it to then
collapse under its own weight
after killing everybody or exiling those
they couldn't kill and then to see the
country sort of wrench back to democracy
on its own not with us though so what
happens even when a country makes it
back to democracy what happens is they
hate the United States right I have
cousins who are just working people
farmers taxi drivers and now they're
members of radical parties the Communist
Party because the United States
actions so put them so damage their
families that they just can't get Paxton
multiply that by 57 you know the Gallup
Organization came out with a poll just
within the past year and they did this
poll in almost every country in the
world obviously there are some countries
that there have access to but in almost
every country in the world
what was the country that is the
greatest threat to human rights because
obviously the Iranians with their movie
business and their submarines in there
so this is not something that is
accidental this isn't something that one
policy gone wrong this is who we are and
it's who we are because we allow it to
happen as as it wouldn't occur to most
other governments on the planet to say
you know what I don't like his politics
and indeed continued other thing that
happened to be when I was at the CIA I
had come back from overseas duty in
Pakistan and I got promoted I became the
executive assistant to the Deputy
Director it's a big job big deal right
you have access to everything so my
first day of the job my boss said to me
well actually I said to him so what are
we doing right I didn't know what I was
supposed to do all I know is that I had
to Steve Jobs what do you want me to do
he said I can't tell you until you sign
these secrecy ratings I said okay I went
up to the seventh floor it's the
executive floor knocked on the door said
I'm supposed to sign some secrecy
greetings I decide six different
documents when I finished signing the
sixth one I said so what gives and the
guy says well and I should tell you this
is in July of 2002 he said next February
we're going to invade Iraq we're going
to overthrow Saddam Hussein and we're
going to open the world's largest Air
Force Base so that we can move all of
our air assets from the Persian Gulf
into Iraq and deprive of a sovereign bin
Laden of the ability to say that we are
polluting the land of the Two Holy
Mosques I looked at this guy like he was
scene and all I could think to stammer
out was we haven't cut deadlines yet I
thought that's what this whole thing was
about were supposed to catch bin Laden
he killed 3,000 Americans and he said
look the decisions been made you can
[__] all you want nobody's gonna listen
to you this is what we're doing and so
that's what we did now a few weeks later
I went back up to his office and I'm
telling you this because this is typical
of what happens in the CIA and the White
House and the Pentagon and even the
State Department I guarantee you it's
happening right now as we speak
I went into his office and he was at his
desk for the white piece of paper and a
box of Crayola markers colored markers I
said what you doing he said oh I'm
designing the new Iraqi flag I said that
maybe the Iraqis should do and he said
no but that's the arrogance that we see
in our policy that's a normal event to
have a gs-15 aircraft designing another
country's flag to be imposed on them by
the way that had exactly the same colors
as the Israeli flag which I'm convinced
was not an accident that's the way
government works in this country I
wanted to also talk about the mechanism
for overthrowing a government you know
there's actually a bureaucracy to this
and this is the thing about the CIA
people think that the CIA is everywhere
and is everything the truth is there are
a lot of morons there are a lot of
Psychopaths and sociopaths we can get
into that a bit but it's a big slow
lumbering bureaucracy just like
everything else uncomfortable and so if
some dope comes up with an idea you know
I want to overthrow let's say the
Venezuelan government there's a process
that goes through there's an office as
crazy as this sounds there's an office
that you go to to overthrow a government
I'm not allowed to say the name of it
it's classified rest assured there's a
certain office that you go to and you
tell the people in this office yeah
there's this I want to overthrow this
government and you know if somebody
Jack's think an object after the plan is
in trade and then you know it'll die but
but I'm gonna overthrow the government
and then say okay well we'll write up a
plan and then we'll see what happens I'm
not making light of this this is honest
to God as God is my witness this is the
way it works this office writes up the
plan and they send it to the Justice
Department
to make sure that it's
it goes to something called the office
of legal counsel
OLC we all know about OLC we all know
about John you and j5e and how they may
denote that stand on its trunk to make
the torture legal in the in the early
part of last decade but it goes to ofc
and LMC while it is supposed to say oh
you know what this is not legal
there are three things that would make
an attack on a foreign country legal
it's very clear everybody knows this is
it's if the country attacks you if you
are invited in by the country or if the
United Nations Security Council votes to
give you the permission to enter the
country that's it that's clear it's
international law but what they do in
OLC is they twist and warp US law to
make it stand on its Trump to justify
this clearly illegal program and they
write this up it's highly classified so
nobody knows about it so don't bother
writing your Congress
you're not and then it goes to the
National Security Council in the White
House well the National Security Council
is amenable so when I say it goes the
National Security Council I mean it goes
to John Bolton it says dear mr. Bolton
the CIA wants to overthrow the
Venezuelan government we think it's
legal for these reasons what do you
think and he says and the Justice
Department thinks it's legal so it must
be legal and he signs it and then it
goes back to the CIA with all the
signatures on it I should say
in the interim he rises the President to
sign up the president finally signs it
and then it goes back to CIA and it sits
in a vault in the operation center and a
copy in a vault in the in the director's
office now I was there the day that the
torture program was approved and I
remember the Deputy Director erupting me
during my briefing repeatedly to say
with me it doesn't torture program is
they just asked for the moon and stars
thinking somebody at some level will say
oh come on we can't do this we can't
waterboard people and murder them and
put them in you know coffins with boxes
of cockroaches to make them insane but
they'll be took anything out and so the
President signed it and the deputy
director kept saying I can't believe the
President signed that memo mark my words
the same thing is happening right now
with Venezuela
somebody at the CIA would remember a
memo we should overthrow the government
of Venezuela justice said that sounds
legal and john bolton said not only does
it so maybe it sounds like a great idea
and that should be US policy and I also
guarantee you that they had the same
conversations about Iran and a half a
dozen other countries and then it went
to the president anybody want to put
money on whether the president sign this
I wouldn't wanna make that better and
then it went to the CEO that's what
happens but in the end nothing good
comes of any of this we've got lessons
learned we've seen what's happened in
Iran and the Dominican Republic and
hawala and Greece and Cyprus and
Honduras and the Philippines and
everywhere else were we overthrowing
governments nothing good ever comes of
it so I would posit and I would say this
to any American if you are a patriot the
only position that you can take is to
oppose this government's position on
Venezuela Becker said I'm better said
we're propagandized as a people
we are fed only what the big
corporations and the US government want
us to three
I don't watch Network Mays anymore of
course myself I won't read till the
sword I want to read our team and
Sputnik and al-jazeera and I mean that's
people ask me where do you get your news
and then besides my personal beef with
MSNBC but I feel like I have to have
alternative news because that's the only
way to really understand what's
happening in the world there's not a
giant conspiracy against the American
people
to trick us into thinking that white
white dough is the legitimate president
of Venezuela one white dough is the
Schmo from GW grad school that nobody
ever heard of and somebody in the White
House said you know what this guy should
be the president he's just some guy from
GE
[Music]
anyway I'm going to keep it short
because it's hot and there are a lot of
us I don't happy to take questions if if
we're doing that kind of thing but thank
you for being here keep up the fight we
got to fight the secret service because
I know in my bones that they're planning
something that's grossly illegal it's a
terrible violation of international law
[Applause]
it was like overnight she drank the
kool-aid and I don't know what the
precipitating event was but I like
Venezuela for example or even Iran I
just can't take her seriously anymore
for forward thinking and progressive how
do we stop our evil country from taking
over these countries self-determination
and taking and feeling their natural
I have determination in the incident
Natural Resources and you know I never
call me naive but they never really gave
that much of a thought until 1991 I was
I was working on Iraq and Kuwait during
the first Gulf War and I was in Saudi
Arabia waiting to go into Kuwait with
the Marines on the bration day which I
did and I said to one of the guys that
play in with us one of the embassy guys
how proud I was to be a part of this to
liberate this country and to liberate
the country and bring democracy and
human rights and he looked at me like I
was nuts this is really this is really a
great day and he said if this country
had gravel its
oil do you think we would give two shits
about what happens please no no and
that's why when the news came out that
Afghanistan has a trillion dollars worth
of rare earth metals should anybody be
surprised that we're still in
Afghanistan no and Venezuela has lots
and lots of oil some say oh it's dirty
oil is full of sulfur it's not like
Libyan oil yeah well guess what
it's a day's boat ride from the
refineries in Texas so I agree with you
at the risk of sounding cynical this is
all about oil and we want their oil
[Music]
we're doing do red pepper again we have
to talk to Brian Becker because I've
never seen anybody organize people at
Brian's ever dose it's ridiculous on no
notice he can turn fifty thousand people
here I think another thing Brian did
that I thought was a stroke of genius
no sooner were the words out of Donald
Trump's mouth that he wants to have a
military grade in his own honor
Brian was standing outside the
Department of Interior and he preserved
all possible parade routes yes sir he
speak to the racial element of this
school because this is why doe 80 black
or something like that is their motto
can I talk to the ratio of component of
this that's an important question and
it's one that really is not being
addressed in any of the mainstream
outlets one who I chose a fascist let's
just call this baby's baby here
the man's a fascist he's aligned with
another fascist Charleson ro in and
Brazilian cities alive with extreme
right-wingers in Colombia and yeah I
mean these are these are the white
people of Latin America there are the
Spanish and Portuguese descendants of
Spanish to Portuguese immigrants in
Latin America they don't like the
indigenous people they took the country
from them they took the resources from
them and by god they hate me in in the
minority and so I think this is all part
of a broader racial issue to keep
indigenous people down and to make sure
that that white right-wingers control
the economies
yes actually they call themselves a
Spaniard experience I've heard that
myself yeah but not just in Venezuela
but elsewhere
no they haven't auto pilot for example
they don't call themselves Guatemalans
they call themselves great question so
in my own experience can I talk about
some of the people that I know what are
the people like in general it's not an
easy answer
most people are there just because
they're patriotic and they think that
they can express their patriotism by
doing whatever it is the CIA wants them
to do whether it's analysis or
operations or if they're scientists they
work in technology the Science and
Technology Directorate they just want to
do something in public service they
think that they're doing the right thing
in the Director of Operations that the
culture is wildly different a CIA
psychiatrist once told me that the CIA
seeks to actively hire people who have
sociopathic tendencies not sociopaths
sociopaths have no conscience they
easily pass a polygraph because they
don't register guilt in any way but it's
easy for a sociopath to slip through the
process because if you don't feel guilt
you don't react to the polygraph and so
here we have people who are Cowboys just
by virtue of their own personal beliefs
and then you train them and give them
weapons and literally unlimited budgets
and you send them overseas I'll give you
one example I won't use his name
although it's out there in the press so
I'm not going to use it as I said
earlier I worked in the counterterrorism
center for many years I sat about 10
feet away from a guy who was working on
Latin American issues he was a nice
enough guy he'd say good morning every
day that's a good morning to him you
know how's your family
nice how was your vacation whatever
I never really was clear on exactly what
he did because he was part of a group
called I won't tell you what he was
called went about it was a it was a very
onerous title for a group it had the
word special in it yeah so they were
doing something special I wasn't ready
to it was after I left the CIA that he
retired and Vanity Fair didn't feature
story about him and as it turns out even
been a hitman for the County cartel
before joining the CIA so he was a mass
murderer but by god he was patriotic and
so they hired him so would they hire him
to do they hired him to kill people
that's all his job was to kill people I
worked good with a guy in the Middle
East just before 9/11
very closely we even we've been groomed
together
overseas and then 9/11 happened and I
lost track of him for about eight weeks
and then I ran into him at home and I
said hey Billy
great big he said
very quietly doing that game stick he
looked at me like I was crazy
this is killing people what do you think
I've been doing and I realized I hadn't
been begging to go to Afghanistan
because I was a fluent Arabic speaker
and they wouldn't send me well they
never do is why they didn't need to
interview anybody capturing people to
interrogate them they were murdering
them so that's that's the attitude
inside the Directorate of operations
there aren't just sociopaths we've
slipped through the cracks there are
psychopaths and I'm going to go one
beyond that too
there are a million psychological
studies out there from the American
Psychiatric Association the American
Psychological Association even in
Psychology Today magazine saying that
virtually every major CEO in America is
associate a clinical associate thing
because the only way that you can work
your way up to that level is to have no
conscience as you clog your way to the
top stepping on the bus and everybody
around you
well this money is a big company just
like any other big organization where
lives are at stake and the stakes are
very high
so of course the CIA's leadership is
going to be made up of sociopaths and
Psychopaths people who can kill without
second thought and go to bed at night
and sleep like a baby and that's not an
organization I wanted to be in video sir
yeah you speak a little bit about Jeana
half full and how it was that she was
invited by tromping her role in the
torture gene and that's why I worked for
Jeana
I wrote a 1,200 weirdo edit The
Washington Post about Gina that's why
the FBI still sits in front of my house
[Music]
Gina asked for Gina in my view Gina's an
associate that she and I'm not saying
anything here that's not been in the
press well Gina was the she was a very
senior officer in the counterterrorism
center when I was there she was a 32
year operational veteran recruiting
spies to steal secrets all over the
world never married devoted solely to
the job and she was a protege of Jose
Rodriguez Jose Rodriguez was the head of
counterterrorism after coca black was
actually the night before I went to
prison
Jose tweeted at me and he said don't
drop the soap ask for
[Music]
Jose I am on the right side of history
and you were not and when Jose became
the deputy director he made Gina the
head of counterterrorism
Gina continued to move up well when she
was the head of counterterrorism she
threw out to one of the secret sites
just to watch the prisoner be torture
not for any other reason she was so
senior it's so important that she really
ought to have just stated in her office
at headquarters thinking the big plots
but she wanted to see and enjoy yeah
and so she did and she's never had to
answer for that
I wrote it up that just recently there
was there was a document that was
Declassified as part of the Guantanamo
hearing on how to Sheikh Mohammed I'm
not joking on page 20 2014 6 but this
document
totally serious they don't release it
all at one time they released a little
bit it said that Gina was the chief of
base at one ton of them during the
torture program nobody knew that so she
has this inner flood she likes this
she's intuitive and I think that that's
that's so incredibly dangerous and sick
that's exactly the person that you don't
want to be in a position like that but
somehow Gina has been able to win over
both the Obama people and the Trump
people because they don't fail all about
her don't forget that she made the
senior service under Obama she ended up
running counterterrorism under Obama and
being made deputy director of the CIA
under Obama Trump just promoted
[Music]
so
social media in the attempted coos it
was used effectively in Nicaragua and
and you know what well actually probably
I have talked about this on our show
when it appeared that the uprising what
was it the Green Revolution I think they
called it in Iran I had a chance of
succeeding Hillary Clinton personally
called Twitter and asked them not to do
their nightly maintenance so that
Twitter would remain up so the
opposition could continue to organize to
overthrow the Iranian government so
there's a real role for social media now
we could do the same kind of thing by
sharing our information on social media
I will advise one note of caution and
that is that the cops are on social
media to not just local cops harassing
you know the wall street protesters I
mean FBI CIA DEA ATF they're all on
social media they all have fake accounts
and they're all spying on us besides the
fact that Facebook Twitter Google
everybody has formal relationships with
the FBI and the CIA so even if they're
not spying on your account Facebook and
Twitter and the others will voluntarily
give your information to them
yes on the other side that's a good
point
on the other side this could be the
savior of some of these democratic
movements if you've got whatsapp but
it's not taking time by the government
or viber for example or signal something
that's encrypted Kalinda Minster could
be covering first where people can hear
you on the other side of you you mean
the people in the street you see listen
we've got right I'm sorry I
misunderstood you how the US subsidizes
it all the ways they've always done this
listen every every English language
radio station in Yemen I'm telling you
from firsthand experience is the
Department of Defense propaganda
operation every one of them and they try
to mimic NPR on purpose they call it in
many voices right but it's all
propaganda this is an active program
used by all the major departments and
agencies to spread propaganda especially
among the youth now this is our taxpayer
money at work that's also something that
you that's very dangerous that our
members of Congress do
for what you do to educate the American
public and we are so grateful that you
came here tonight for a very historic
talk in at a very critical moment in
Venezuelans history so if you could all
stop your live streaming and your
filming and you can stop